fabchannel.com 2008-12-17

# PRIVACY POLICY | Fabchannel Infopages

## PRIVACY POLICY

Tuesday, June 3rd, 2008 at 10:07 pm 

Privacy Statement

Fabchannel.com is an online service for live concerts from Paradiso and Melkweg in Amsterdam, The Roxy on Sunset in W. Hollywood and Sala Bikini and Sala Apolo in Barcelona. Fabchannel cares a lot about its users’ online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at privacy@fabchannel.com.

Personal information  
Fabchannel.com collects user submitted information such as nickname, email address, country of residence, gender and age to authenticate users. We will never sell any of the e-mail addresses to third parties. We may use a user’s email address to send updates, newsletters or news regarding the Fabchannel services if the user is subscribed to the newsletter. Users may unsubscribe to email of this type by logging into their Fabchannel account and deselecting the corresponding checkbox in “My Settings”. 

Fabchannel.com also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes. 

User Profile information including members’ pictures and nicknames are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction on the Fabchannel Web site. Users communicate on Fabchannel with each other through the Fabchannel services without disclosing their email addresses. 

Cookies  
Cookies are small text files that are saved on your hard disk or in the memory of your computer. They can be used to save your preferences for a service. Cookies can’t damage your computer or files. If you don’t want to accept cookies you can change the settings in your browser. Certain features may not be accessible with your cookies switched-off. 

In the future our privacy statement may be updated. The changes can then be found on this page, so we recommend you to visit this page regularly. 

Contacting the Web Site  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at: privacy@fabchannel.com (Fabchannel B.V., Kleine-Gartmanplantsoen 21, 1017 RP Amsterdam, The Netherlands) .
